Okay
So earlier
We have already covered the corresponding defined
We have explained the three basic functions
Next, let's look at the other two functions of DEFI
One is our corresponding workflow
one is TELEFLOW
which is our chat workflow
Now let's take a look at the corresponding TELEFLOW
First, let's look at the test
E s t
Now let's look at its most basic page, okay
Starting from this feature
You'll notice that the entire page is completely different
It's a world of difference compared to before.
Previously,
Actually, we were operating in a single window
Now with this menu item,
Actually, the entire page layout has been modified as a whole.
As for these modifications
Let me show you one by one
Well, first is still the corresponding layout.
Our previous page was actually very inflexible.
With this in place
It functions as a page layout
You can freely drag and adjust it yourself
or we can accomplish any kind of function we want
Let's start by explaining this layout clearly.
First of all, the current layout above
These functions are actually all the same
are all consistent publishing and such
And the main part is on the left
This is also the same
For example, we deploy some
or the access API
Then, regarding some of the access logs,
And as for our corresponding monitoring section,
There are some important functions in this middle section.
The first one is to add a node
This node is currently on the page
What you can operate on are these block-by-block contents.
This is what we refer to as the node
There are many nodes that can be operated.
For example, if we want to operate the corresponding large model
perform Knowledge retrieval
reply to the corresponding content
Then there's the question classifier, conditional branching, iteration loops
as well as our corresponding code execution
I want to perform some operations or make HTTP requests, etc.
So this is where we can add nodes or add tools
This part is all feasible
This is what we refer to as a node.
Moving on to the next part
which we refer to as annotation
For example, I want to add to a certain content
add a comment to this node
Hey
What is this function for?
This is calling the large model, okay
So this is the function of adding annotations
You can see it's also a node
You can drag it yourself, okay?
Or if you don't need it, just delete it.
Alright, then let's move on to look at
It is a pointer
pointer function
The pointer function
It means we are fixing the page in place
in terms of our page operations
is in a local area
Or there is also a manual mode
you can drag the corresponding page by yourself
The upper part is fixed
It's like we have a fixed window here.
Zooming in and out works the same way
Then below is where we adjust the nodes
For example, I want to adjust a suitable layout or something.
We still use the manual mode.
It depends on how you want to use it, okay?
Then there's also the corresponding full-screen option
maximize the page, okay
These are some additional features we've added.
Next, let's take a look at some of the most core
the most basic nodes
After we have created a set flow
it only provides you with three nodes
Let's take a look at these three nodes one by one
The first node is called User Input
After clicking on the node,
On your right
It will display some information about the current node
For example, what will we display?
The first one is the Settings content
Another one is the last execution
What was the purpose of the last execution?
that is the chat history we display
What are the functions available in the Settings?
The first one is the input field
You can choose the input fields yourself.
For example, we add a text variable
just like what we used before
It's the same way as before
For example, I want to add a paragraph
or to add a radio button
or checkboxes
you can make selections in the chat window
I'll explain it to you later
Actually, it will have two default contents
Come on
The first default of the two defaults corresponds to the user input
Query
So what is this
it's the system variable, okay
What is the first system variable?
called the user input question
Okay
Let me first demonstrate how to make the call, okay?
we click on preview
After clicking on the preview
Let's first take a look at the most basic page.
For example, if I reply with a
Hello, can you see it?
Can you see the difference?
Now let's think about this issue
This is the same as the previous usage, right?
There is no difference
But what's the difference compared to before?
You will see that after each node is executed
there will also be a green checkmark at the end
Okay
This is the execution process
So, I'll execute this one first
then execute this one
Then execute this one, okay
If an issue occurs while running a node
It will mark you with a cross
For example, if the current node reports an error or encounters some issue
Then the content is actually the same.
Similarly, we can click on its detailed execution
But what exactly is the execution logic? Okay
Now, let's first look at the initial input content
Overall execution flow
This is the input content
What is the input content?
is the input performed by the current start node
It has some default parameters
For example, the first one is the system file
because we have some, uh, windows
We can provide files
or provide images and so on
This is the information for providing files.
And there's also this UC ID
This is the ID information of the current user.
Because we will have many users logging in later on.
Many users can access your account and such.
and then app id
Then there are some IDs of this working workflow.
And also, for example, the corresponding running ID
This is the question raised by our user.
Next is the number of inspections by our system, okay
So where does this come from?
Actually, what we just saw are two things.
one is the user query
This is what we just saw
Another one is the user's FA
Now, for the remaining few
for example, the user's ID
and also like our corresponding workflow ID
So what is this used for?
It is actually used
Because in this workflow stage
It actually has a feature called memory function
called memory
But we don't actually need to consider the memory function.
this memory function
If we want to implement it ourselves through code
it is relatively more complex
So here,
In DEFI
How does this workflow record
your conversation
is through these IDs
This information can be used for recording.
Next is the corresponding output
The output content is what we get after invoking the large model
the information output to you
Then the information we output, well, one is the corresponding, um,
This is the user's thought
Then there is our corresponding reply, okay
This is the complete execution process.
Then the tracking process is actually the same as before
First is the user input
Then the data is processed, but there is nothing to output.
what is the output information
Then comes the large model
the information received by the large model
The input content corresponds to
Hello
It will convert the data into a prompt.
Do you see it
It has transformed it into data for the prompt.
Then, your mode is a chat mode.
The file is empty.
This is the user input content
And then there's the prompt information
a token of the prompt
Then some printed data information of the prompt
Some information will be recorded here
Then comes the output content from our model
The output information looks like this
There is also a direct reply
Show him the direct reply
This direct reply compared to our previous one
Actually, why is there such a thing?
Isn't the large model here directly replying?
Why is there this current, um, direct reply thing?
But I already have such a step above
there is this thing
Why is there another one below
Why don't I just directly output from the large model, right?
Why is there
Because later on
What I display now can be defined by myself
For example, I only display the content replied by the large model
but some data, for example, I don't want to show to the user
You can set it up yourself
So it separates the two functions, okay
This is its overall workflow
Next, let's take a look at each specific process within the workflow
what each node does
The first one is the start node
As for the start node, well, not much is shown here.
He only showed two
one is fail
one is query
There should actually be something like the last run
displayed from the last run
there should be these UI IDs or
app id these would have system defaults
but it is not displayed here
Then there's our next step
after our current node completes execution
what to do next
For example, the next node I'm going to execute is this large model
So, the first step in the large model should be clearly explained to everyone, right?
some content entered by the user
the user's input questions
as well as the files and other data transmitted by our users
for example, adding fields
You can set the restrictions yourself.
Let's get familiar first
Then let's move on to the second node
that is, my LMOK, how you want to write this name
You can determine it yourself
For example, this node is for calling the large model.
You can determine it yourself.
You can give it a corresponding name yourself.
Next, let's look at the corresponding part, which also has the last execution
It displays the corresponding data.
We are recording his information, okay
The first model can be selected by yourself
For example, which model do we choose
For example, we use Qwen, right?
or what other models we use
can be determined by yourself
For example, we can switch to the corresponding chain3's max, okay
Looking further ahead
there will also be something called context
What is the context?
as we mentioned before
Will there be a Knowledge?
Knowledge base Knowledge base
We will generate the corresponding context
Then we will add the data from the knowledge base here
Currently, we don't have this and therefore don't need to add it.
Then here is the system prompt
This system prompt is to tell the large model hey
What is your current role?
For example, you are a translation assistant.
This is the system prompt
You can also add information
For example, I want to add a round of conversation
I want the large model to know
what I roughly want to do
For example, this assigns a role to the user
If you want to add or convert this danmu (bullet comment) reply
or you can add it here
He said, well, this is a question raised by the user
Hello
Or say, hey, I'm Baichuan
then the next time it remembers
he knows oh
So this user is Baichuan, okay
Then let's look further
It has a memory function
The memory function is built-in.
Do you see it?
There is also a built-in memory function
Who performs the memory function
When we receive user input,
It actually has corresponding information
this this this will have this information
used to record your memory function
Then looking further ahead
it will have content defined as user user
which is actually the same as the questions asked by our users
Let's delete it first.
Alright, so these are the questions raised by the user U
or forwarded from the first node to you
So the data we can receive
How do I get the corresponding content?
is a forward slash
For example, we have the academic data obtained from the previous node
and some system prompts in the
For example, there is the ID in the system
This is what we saw earlier
One is the system
one is user input
User input refers to the information entered here.
We have two user inputs, right?
One is a file
one is the user's question
Okay
then here
For example, I want to retrieve the user's question, right?
called user
called query
Take it over, okay
So now this is the question raised by the user
Then whether there is memory and how many rounds of memory
For example, if you want to remember as much as you want
you can fill it in yourself
Also, note that the more rounds of memory you have
you will consume more tokens
So we generally set it up like this
the corresponding number of rounds will be limited
Then there's something like visual learning,
because we have some models
It supports this kind of image recognition
or our image processing
If the model doesn't support this feature, then you can't click on it.
And then there is, for example, enabling the corresponding inference
Then there's the thinking mode
Then let's look at what comes next
our output variables
What are the output variables?
Let's first look at the input variables, which are from the large model
after the user's question
it actually needs to output some content
The first one is the corresponding text output by the large model.
and then there's the content we've been contemplating
that is, the content of the thought mode
Next is the usage information
We will inform you, um
how many tokens were used in this instance
and how many tokens the image prompt has
token and so on
Then there will be something called a failure retry hypothesis below
After this error occurs
How many times do you want to retry
because we have some of what is actually called robustness properties
the robustness mechanism
We try our best to avoid some errors.
This can also be set by yourself.
Then, how to handle exceptions
For example, if an error occurs in the exception branch
we need to call something else
Then proceed to the next step
what we need to do next
just reply directly
So what exactly is included in the direct reply?
First, the information we reply with in the Settings
It adds a call to the large model
So how many output contents should there be when calling the large model?
We currently only have one
In fact, there would be three
as we just saw, there are actually three
For example, there is taste
Let's say we output all three, okay
Test
And there's also the corresponding content of the thought
Furthermore, for example
I want to output some of the user's information
Why are these two nodes separated?
on this point
Actually, there are some pieces of information that I don't want the user to know.
For example, how many tokens you've consumed
how much data is consumed
But these are things I don't want users to know
Therefore, we can choose two nodes for output.
Now, these are the three most basic nodes we have
its functionality and how to invoke it
I'll also publish it
Let's see the effect
Let's preview it now
Let's ask a question
Hello
Well, you'll notice the data I'm providing now
It contains a lot of content.
For example, the first one is our reply from the large model
the content replied to you taste
Then, the second one is some information about our thoughts.
Because the current model does not have the form of thinking
You can switch to a thinking model
For example, some of our thoughts um
Hmm, let's change this. It seems like the correct one, right?
Wait a moment, hello
You will notice that the output information
has become one is the output from our large model
And then there's also the thought process, right?
And another one is the corresponding current prompt.
how many tokens does it use
For example, its price is called 0.016
How much did this cost
Then how many are being used?
This actually shows how much was used and what the price is
Blah blah blah and so on
which is to record the consumption of your current conversation.
What are the contents of the consumption?
OK then these things
Actually, we don't need to display it
So we will make this DEFI platform
is split into two parts
but the content we want to display
We generally refer to the output of the large model.
if we don't want it
Just delete it directly
Let's take a look at the data refresh
Hello
Alright, now we can see its input information
there won't be those price-related parts
So this is the most basic way of using it in the workflow
One is the input of our node
then call the large model
then directly reply
Then add a demonstration for it
Baichuan
Remember
the large model in this usage process
it actually does not provide
does not have this memory function
it doesn't know what your previous round of conversation was
For example, let me add another one 'Who am I'
OK, now it has this memory function
The so-called memory function
our single-modal form is stateless
This should be the most fundamental point for everyone to understand.
Because it does not have a memory function.
However, in the case of DEFI
This workflow includes this feature
It automatically helps you achieve this memory function.
So this is the most basic way to use our workflow.
It's not the most basic usage of our cha flow